Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers
1976-2004
M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
200.0 Linear feet 100 manuscript boxes, 90 record storage containers
A collection of archival papers, audio-visual media, publications, artifacts, photographs, letters, and other documents connected to Hershman-Leeson's art works and projects created since the 1970s and through 2003.
Hershman-Leeson, Lynn, 1941-
Scope and Content
Related Collections
Women art revolution: videotape interviews by Lynn Hershman-Leeson for film, 1990-2008, M1639. A digital collection containing the video interviews, as well as transcripts, is available online at http://lib.stanford.edu/women-art-revolution.
Biographical Note
Lynn Hershman Leeson (b. 1941) is a performance artist and filmmaker who, in various media, has investigated the idea of selfhood and what establishes an individual as a sentient, gendered, unique person. Between the years of 1974 and 1978, Hershman Leeson spent much of her time performing as an alter ego, the character Roberta Breitmore. Much of the work--drawings, photographs, clothing, medical records, letters, etc.--Hershman Leeson produced during the Breitmore years related to the character's emotional and practical existences. Hershman Leeson seemed to be demonstrating that the two existences could and should not be easily separated--nor should the artist herself be easily separated from the character she created. Hershman Leeson's work in film, video, and new media has been equally focused toward exploring the ways that bodies interact and define themselves. Lorna (1983-84), described by the artist as "the first interactive video art disc," allowed the viewer to experience the emotions of the title character while also, at key points, making important decisions for her. The viewer was both entwined with and removed from Lorna's life. In the 1980s and 90s, Hershman continued to focus on new media, expanding her work in video and creating online environments that incorporated artificial intelligence. Concurrently, she began to direct feature films; her first film, Conceiving Ada (1997), situated the nineteenth-century computer science innovator Ada Lovelace in juxtaposition with the twentieth-century computer reality that she helped to create. A winner of numerous awards and honors for her contributions to art practice, Hershman Leeson is currently Chair of the Film Department at the San Francisco Art Institute. She is Professor Emerita at the University of California, Davis, and an A.D. White Professor at large at Cornell University. !Women Art Revolution reflects years of interviews that Hershman Leeson has compiled in order to tell the story of the feminist art movement in the artists' own words.
Access to Collection
Open for research. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Hershman-Leeson, Lynn, 1941-
Container List
- Series 1: Audio-Visual Materials, 1
  - Subseries 1.01: America's Finest, 1.01
    - [VHS Dub]; 1994 (2 items), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:02:30:00 (Carton 36, Folder 1)
    - America's Finest Doc; 1995-05-30 (1 item), Video: 8mm Video; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 36, Folder 2)
    - [dubs + Amsterdam Lecture]; 1994-10-25; 1995-05-30 (3 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 36, Folder 3)
    - America's Finest 1994; 1994 (1 item), Video: Hi8; [unidentified element] (Carton 36, Folder 4)
    - America's Finest Documentation; 1995-06 (1 item), Video: SVHS; [unidentified element]; 30 min.; 00:09:00:00 (Carton 36, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1.02: Beautiful People/Beautiful Friends, 1.02
    - Beautiful People; 1994-08-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: 1/4" open reel; Original (Carton 28, Folder 1)
    - [VHS Dub]; 1994 (2 items), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 28, Folder 2)
    - 2 versions of beautiful friends,, the genius of AGB, transferred from Audio; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 28, Folder 3)
    - Beautiful Master with TC; 1994-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 28, Folder 4)
    - Transfer from 3/4 Copy of Film; 1994-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 28, Folder 5)
    - [various footage]; 1994 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 28, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 1.03: The B-Files, 1.03
    - The B Files; undated (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 90 min. (Carton 39, Folder 1)
    - B-Files; 1997-03-24 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 32 min. (Carton 39, Folder 2)
    - [The B-Files Dubs]; 1997 (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 39, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 1.04: Catfish, 1.04
    - Catfish; 1987-12 (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 17, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.05: Chain Reaction, 1.05
    - Chain Reaction Reel 2; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm Full Coat Magnetic; Soundtrack (Carton 27, Folder 1)
    - News/Chain Reaction; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master (Carton 39)
    - Chain Reaction; 1983 (1 item), Audio: Cassette; Dub (Carton 39, Folder 4)
    - NewTime Edited Master; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 5)
    - Jello Biafra Tape 1; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 6)
    - Sample Excerpts from Art and Artists Programs; 1983 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 7)
    - [Various Footage]; undated (3 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.06: Conceiving Ada, 1.06
    - [Selects Roll #1-10]; 1997 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 1, Folder 1)
    - [Selects Roll #1-10]; 1997 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 2, Folder 1)
    - Final Mix Master; 1997-06-11 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm three track magnetic; Master (Carton 2, Folder 2)
    - Reel 21, 22; 1996-07-12 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 2, Folder 3)
    - Conceiving Ada R41-42, 44-47; 1996-07 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 3, Folder 1)
    - Reel 52-57; 1996-07-21 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative; 00:09:45:00 (Carton 4, Folder 1)
    - Cut Pix For Optical Line-up; 1997-08-22 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 4, Folder 2)
    - Selects Roll #17-20, 23-24; 1997 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 4, Folder 3)
    - Reel 49-51; 1996-07-18 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative; 00:08:45:00 (Carton 4, Folder 4)
    - [Various Footage and film to tape transfers]; undated (21 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; [16] 30 min, [1] 10 min., [4] 5 min. (Carton 5, Folder 1)
    - [Conceiving Ada DigiBeta to Beta SP xfer]; undated (11 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 5 min., 30 min. (Carton 5, Folder 2)
    - [various footage]; undated (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; [3] 30 min., [1] 10 min. (Carton 5, Folder 3)
    - [Conceiving Ada Footage]; undated (11 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 5, Folder 4)
    - [Conceiving Ada Footage]; undated (9 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 1)
    - [Conceiving Ada Footage]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 6, Folder 2)
    - Final Corrected Version; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 6, Folder 3)
    - Main Title Animation; 1997-07-19 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 6, Folder 4)
    - [Ada Avid Cut Dub Reels 1-9]; 1997-06-24 (9 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 6, Folder 5)
    - Conceiving Ada w/ Final Stereo Mix Avid Cut; 1997-06-24 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min.; 00:84:33:00 (Carton 6, Folder 6)
    - [Alpha Master]; 1996-08 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 7)
    - Tim Leary; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 8)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 9)
    - Tape #1 Emmy on Talk Show; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 10)
    - [various footage]; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element] (Carton 6, Folder 11)
    - [Ada Avid Layoffs]; 1997-05-27 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 10 min. (Carton 6, Folder 12)
    - God's Dog & Rose Transfer from DAT; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 13)
    - Tilda V.O. 001; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 14)
    - sound of babbage engine BAVC Master Tape, God's Dog - old; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 15)
    - Tilda V.O. 002; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 16)
    - Audio [illegible] Babbage, Engine; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 6, Folder 17)
    - [various footage, interviews, auditions]; undated (4 items), Video: Hi8; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 7, Folder 1)
    - [Final Avid Cut]; 1997 (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 7, Folder 2)
    - Ruff Conceiving Ada Part 1; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 7, Folder 3)
    - Reel 1, 4, 5; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 7, Folder 4)
    - [various footage, EDLs]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 90 min. (Carton 7, Folder 5)
    - [film to tape transfer, VTR 001-022]; undated (21 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 7, Folder 6)
    - [Conceiving Ada CR. 65, 38, 52-57 ]; 1997-01-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 7, Folder 7)
    - Music 001; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 7, Folder 8)
    - Conceiving Ada; (1 item), Video: VHS; Commercial; 00:00:85:00 (Carton 8, Folder 1)
    - Conceiving Ada Reel Dubs R1-R9; 1997 (29 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 10 min. (Carton 8, Folder 2)
    - Conceiving Ada; 1997 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 00:85:00:00 (Carton 8, Folder 3)
    - [Conceiving ada various footage]; undated (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 8, Folder 4)
    - Ada Golden Gate Copy #3-9; 1996-07-30 (7 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 180 min. (Carton 9, Folder 9)
    - Conceiving Ada Golden Gate #3-9 Copy; 1996-07-30 (7 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 180 min. (Carton 9, Folder 9)
    - Ada SR 010A-012A Copy; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 180 min. (Carton 9, Folder 9)
    - ADA SR 001, 007-015; undated (10 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 10 min. (Carton 9, Folder 9)
    - ADA SR 003 30 FPS non-drop Copy; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 180 min. (Carton 9, Folder 9)
    - [SR Copy 002, 004-006, 011]; undated (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 180 min. (Carton 10, Folder 10)
    - Protection Master, Original Master; undated (15 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Master; 180 min. (Carton 10, Folder 10)
    - [Protection Master 10A-12A]; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Master; 180 min. (Carton 10, Folder 10)
    - T. Leary, bante commercials + windows part 1; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 11, Folder 11)
    - [3/4 Avid Cut Dub Reels 1-9]; 1997 (8 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 11, Folder 11)
    - [Alpha Reel 1B-6B]; 1996-07 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 11, Folder 11)
    - [Alpha Reel 7B, 9B-11B]; 1996-08 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 11, Folder 11)
    - [Print Masters Reel 1-9]; undated (9 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Dub; 15 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Music and Effects Reel 1-9]; undated (9 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Dub; 15 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Music and Effects reels 1-9]; undated (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Music and Effects reels 1-9 Backup]; undated (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Reels 1-9]; undated (12 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Reels 1-9 Backup]; undated (12 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Ada Tapes 1-3, 4(x2), 5-11; 1996-07-24 (12 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; Master; 30 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Misc. DATs]; undated (7 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Audio: DAT; [unidentified element] (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Ada DIA/DIAL]; undated (5 items), Audio: DAT; [unidentified element]; 124 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [music]; undated (2 items), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element] (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - Changes only from Bob Dalva Avid; 1997-03-25 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 32 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Leary Footage/Babbage footage; undated (4 items), Video: Mini DV; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [footage masters]; 1996 (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 32 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [Composite Master]; 1996 (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 32 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - Charlene Flies, Fireplace Scene, Death Scene; 1996-12-16 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; [unidentified element]; 32 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [various edited master footage]; undated (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 64 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - [various footage]; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 12 min., 32 min. (Carton 12, Folder 12)
    - for [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 45, Folder 1)
    - R.U. Sirius Mondo 2000; 1992-03-27 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 45, Folder 2)
    - Reels 28, 34, 37, 40; 1996-07 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 48, Folder 1)
    - Conceiving Ada Reel #11; 1996-07-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 48, Folder 2)
    - Orginal Negative Selects Roll 11-13, 15, 18-19; 1997 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 48, Folder 3)
    - Reel 20; 1996-07-12 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 49, Folder 1)
    - Reel 80; 1996-09-09 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 16mm; Negative (Carton 49, Folder 2)
    - Reel 64-65, 70-71; 1996-07 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 49, Folder 3)
    - Conceiving Ada Original Negative Selects Roll #1; 1997-06-10 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 49, Folder 4)
    - Reel 62; 1996-07-22 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 55, Folder 1)
    - Conceiving Ada Reels #29-32, #35-36, 39; 1996-07 (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 55, Folder 2)
    - Reel 69; 1996-07-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 56, Folder 1)
    - Reel 23; 1996-07-14 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 56, Folder 2)
    - Reel 33; 1996-07-15 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 56, Folder 3)
    - Reel 38; 1996-07 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 56, Folder 4)
    - Comp Dupe Neg, Uncut 35mm, Roll Ada 002; 1997-07-28 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 56, Folder 5)
    - Conceiving Ada Original Negative Selects Roll #2-7; 1997-06-10 (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 57, Folder 1)
    - Reel 59-61; 1996-07-21 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 58, Folder 1)
    - End Crawl; 1997-08-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 58, Folder 2)
    - Conceiving Ada select rolls #21-24; 1997-07 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 58, Folder 3)
    - [Conceiving Ada various footage]; 1997 (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 58, Folder 4)
    - [FX reel]; 1996 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 32 min. (Carton 59, Folder 1)
    - [FX and animations]; 1996 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 2)
    - [Animations]; 1996 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 6 min. (Carton 59, Folder 3)
    - [Film to tape Transfers]; 1996-1999 (9 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 32 min. (Carton 59, Folder 4)
    - Film to Tape Transfer: CR. 63, 69, 49-51 & 34 (selects); 1997-01-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 5)
    - [ADA Reel 01-06]; 1997-03-28 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 6)
    - [Timothy Leary footage]; 1996 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 7)
    - [Timothy Leary footage]; 1996 (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 8)
    - [CR 20-23, 25, 27, 36]; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 32 min. (Carton 59, Folder 9)
    - Ada Sony Demo; 1996-11 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 6 min.; 00:02:23:00 (Carton 59, Folder 10)
    - Francesca Mirror; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 11)
    - Selected Clips; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Master; 12 min. (Carton 59, Folder 12)
    - Robotics; 1996-04-27, Chico MacMuntney (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 59, Folder 13)
    - Rear Screen Projection, Tilda Swinton; 1996-07-23 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 1)
    - Bruce Sterling, Alive Artificial Life Interaction, Steve Part 1; 1996-02-08 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 2)
    - Bruce Sterling, Austin, TX; 1996-02-01 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: SVHS; Dub; 120 min. (Carton 60, Folder 3)
    - Conceiving Ada Dub from DigiBeta Master; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 120 min. (Carton 60, Folder 4)
    - Reel 2; 1997-01-29 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min.; 00:25:00:00 (Carton 60, Folder 5)
    - Foetus, Rappa Edit of CD ROM [illegible]; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 10 min. (Carton 60, Folder 6)
    - Leary, Karen Black; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 7)
    - Tape #1; 1996-04-27, Chico MacMutrey (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 8)
    - ADA Doc; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 60, Folder 9)
    - [Timothy Leary footage]; undated (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 10)
    - [God's Dog Footage]; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min., 5 min. (Carton 60, Folder 11)
    - [God's Dog Footage]; undated ( item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 12 min. (Carton 60, Folder 12)
    - [God's Dog Footage]; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: VHS; Dub; 15 min, 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 13)
    - John as Narrator; 1996-04-30 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 60, Folder 14)
    - [Composite Reel 1A, 2A, 4A, 6A]; 1996-07 (4 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 32 min. (Carton 60, Folder 15)
    - [Composite Master Reel 7A, 9A-11A, 12A; 1996-08 (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Digital Betacam; Master; 32 min. (Carton 60, Folder 16)
    - [Ada Mag track]; 1997-08-20 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35 mm 3-trk Mag; Soundtrack (Carton 61, Folder 1)
    - Reel 26, 27; 1996-07-14 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35 mm; Negative (Carton 61, Folder 2)
    - Reel 66-68, 72-73; 1996-07 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 61, Folder 3)
    - Reel 63; 1996-07-22 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 61, Folder 4)
    - Reel 24, 25; 1996-07-14 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 61, Folder 5)
    - Video Roll 3, 4 (pickups); 1997 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 62, Folder 1)
    - #623A-623B, #623F-623H, #623C-623D, #632 ADA A/B and #623 ADA Pick Ups; 1997 (9 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 62, Folder 2)
    - Video Roll 1a-1c, 2a-2b; 1997 (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 63, Folder 1)
    - Reel #19; 1996-07 (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 63, Folder 2)
    - [Pix and Trims]; undated (19 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; [unidentified element] (Carton 64, Folder 1)
    - Reel #1-4; 1996-07 (2 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 64, Folder 2)
    - Reel #1-10, 12-18; 1996-07 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 65, Folder 1)
    - Orginal Negative Selects Roll 8-10, 14, 16-17; 1997-06-10 (6 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Negative (Carton 66, Folder 1)
    - Cut Pix Reel 1-5a; undated (5 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Film: 35mm; Work Print (Carton 67, Folder 1)